{
    "id": "88e7a63377734ed78848da261517a594",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You won't get the job ............................. you pass the test.",
            "description": "Unless means if not. It is used to express a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have always wished I .............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would sing",
                "could sing",
                "should sing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must learn to stand up .............................. yourself.",
            "description": "To stand up for yourself is to defend yourself. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody thought she would be brave enough to stand up ............................... him.",
            "description": "To stand up to somebody is to not allow them to treat you badly.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "against",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Please tell ................................. to leave.",
            "description": "There is no preposition before tell and its object.",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "to him",
                "of him"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. they worked overtime, they could not finish the project on time.",
            "description": "Although is a conjunction. It is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I would be grateful if you ............................... help me with this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When plants die, they give ............................... gases such as carbon dioxide.",
            "description": "To give something off is to produce it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time you ..............................",
            "description": "We use a past tense with a present meaning after It is time.",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "have left",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………… older than his wife.",
            "description": "We cannot use very with comparative adjectives.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "very",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you wearing ………………………… your sweater?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "below",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got ………………………… razor blades?",
            "description": "We use any in questions and some in affirmative sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}